[
  {
    "question": "سانجي",
    "answer": "س ا ن ج ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "لوفي",
    "answer": "ل و ف ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "زورو",
    "answer": "ز و ر و"
  },
  {
    "question": "نامي",
    "answer": "ن ا م ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناروتو",
    "answer": "ن ا ر و ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساسكي",
    "answer": "س ا س ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساكورا",
    "answer": "س ا ك و ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ديكو",
    "answer": "د ي ك و"
  },
  {
    "question": "يوني",
    "answer": "ي و ن ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ياسو",
    "answer": "ي ا س و"
  },
  {
    "question": "غوكو",
    "answer": "غ و ك و"
  },
  {
    "question": "فيجيتا",
    "answer": "ف ي ج ي ت ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "بولما",
    "answer": "ب و ل م ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كارما",
    "answer": "ك ا ر م ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ياماتو",
    "answer": "ي ا م ا ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "كاكاشي",
    "answer": "ك ا ك ا ش ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايرين",
    "answer": "ا ي ر ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "جيرايا",
    "answer": "ج ي ر ا ي ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "هيناتا",
    "answer": "ه ي ن ا ت ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "شينجي",
    "answer": "ش ي ن ج ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايزن",
    "answer": "ا ي ز ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايتاشي",
    "answer": "ا ي ت ا ش ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "مادارا",
    "answer": "م ا د ا ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "هاشيراما",
    "answer": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساي",
    "answer": "س ا ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "زيرو",
    "answer": "ز ي ر و"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساسوري",
    "answer": "س ا س و ر ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ديدارا",
    "answer": "د ي د ا ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كونان",
    "answer": "ك و ن ا ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "توبي",
    "answer": "ت و ب ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "زابوزا",
    "answer": "ز ا ب و ز ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "رين",
    "answer": "ر ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناغاتو",
    "answer": "ن ا غ ا ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "باين",
    "answer": "ب ا ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "كيلوا",
    "answer": "ك ي ل و ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايلومي",
    "answer": "ا ي ل و م ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "جين",
    "answer": "ج ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "جونو",
    "answer": "ج و ن و"
  },
  {
    "question": "ماركو",
    "answer": "م ا ر ك و"
  },
  {
    "question": "روجر",
    "answer": "ر و ج ر"
  },
  {
    "question": "راموس",
    "answer": "ر ا م و س"
  },
  {
    "question": "كاتاكوري",
    "answer": "ك ا ت ا ك و ر ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "دراغون",
    "answer": "د ر ا غ و ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "رايلي",
    "answer": "ر ا ي ل ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "كوما",
    "answer": "ك و م ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "سابو",
    "answer": "س ا ب و"
  },
  {
    "question": "كوبي",
    "answer": "ك و ب ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "شيراهوشي",
    "answer": "ش ي ر ا ه و ش ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "مونكي دي لوفي",
    "answer": "م و ن ك ي د ي ل و ف ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ارمين",
    "answer": "ا ر م ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "جيمبي",
    "answer": "ج ي م ب ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "راينر",
    "answer": "ر ا ي ن ر"
  },
  {
    "question": "بيرتولد",
    "answer": "ب ي ر ت و ل د"
  },
  {
    "question": "ميكو",
    "answer": "م ي ك و"
  },
  {
    "question": "باراماونت",
    "answer": "ب ا ر ا م ا و ن ت"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساي",
    "answer": "س ا ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "تشوبر",
    "answer": "ت ش و ب ر"
  },
  {
    "question": "هاشيراما",
    "answer": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "جوكو",
    "answer": "ج و ك و"
  },
  {
    "question": "انوس",
    "answer": "ا ن و س"
  },
  {
    "question": "بيروس",
    "answer": "ب ي ر و س"
  },
  {
    "question": "هيسوكا",
    "answer": "ه ي س و ك ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ميليوداس",
    "answer": "م ي ل ي و د ا س"
  },
  {
    "question": "اليزابيث",
    "answer": "ا ل ي ز ا ب ي ث"
  },
  {
    "question": "باندورا",
    "answer": "ب ا ن د و ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايس",
    "answer": "ا ي س"
  },
  {
    "question": "الان",
    "answer": "ا ل ا ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "شيزو",
    "answer": "ش ي ز و"
  },
  {
    "question": "هيكارو",
    "answer": "ه ي ك ا ر و"
  },
  {
    "question": "روديوس",
    "answer": "ر و د ي و س"
  },
  {
    "question": "ايزومي",
    "answer": "ا ي ز و م ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "كينتو",
    "answer": "ك ي ن ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "لايت",
    "answer": "ل ا ي ت"
  },
  {
    "question": "موساشي",
    "answer": "م و س ا ش ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "جينتو",
    "answer": "ج ي ن ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "سيشومارو",
    "answer": "س ي ش و م ا ر و"
  },
  {
    "question": "شيا",
    "answer": "ش ي ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناتسو",
    "answer": "ن ا ت س و"
  },
  {
    "question": "هارو",
    "answer": "ه ا ر و"
  },
  {
    "question": "رين",
    "answer": "ر ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "اورا",
    "answer": "ا و ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "بانا",
    "answer": "ب ا ن ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "جينوس",
    "answer": "ج ي ن و س"
  },
  {
    "question": "سيكي",
    "answer": "س ي ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ماركو",
    "answer": "م ا ر ك و"
  }
]
